http://online.bridgebase.com/intro/privacy.php

Bridge Base Online Privacy Statement
(last updated: May 2012)
Bridge Base Online ("BBO") is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy statement applies to the data collected by BBO through the Bridge Base Online web pages
and the original BBO program (collectively, the Site); it does not apply to data collected through other online or offline BBO sites, products or services.
Collection of your personal information
We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you or allows us to contact you.
We will ask you for your username and password during the registration process. We will ask for it again each time you log in and occasionally during the session.
You need not enter your real name or email address in either the registration form or your profile. The public portion of your profile (Name, email, country, skill level, other information) will be visible to every other member of the site.
If you choose to engage in commerce on our site, we may ask you for your real name, address, telephone number, and credit card details. You can opt to have us remember your name, address, and telephone number and credit card expiration date as a convenience for you.
We will not store your credit card number or credit card security code.
If you choose to play in tournaments sponsored by a National Bridge Organization ( "NBO" -- for example, the ACBL ) we
will ask you for your player number in that NBO to allow us to report your results.
We record visitor IP addresses, usernames, and many details of site activity.
We may record all chat, including private chat between usernames.
We record hands played on the site. This information is made publicly available.
Use of Your Personal Information
The personal information collected will be used to operate the Site and to provide the service(s) or carry out the transaction(s) you have requested or authorized.
In support of these uses, BBO may use personal information to provide you with more effective customer service, to improve the Site and any related BBO products or services, and to make the Site easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information or by customizing the Site to your particular preference or interests.
We may use your personal information to provide you with important information about the product or service that you are using, including critical updates and notifications
We may use your personal information to provide you with information about products or services you may be interested in.
Personal information collected on the Site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which BBO or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using the Site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.
Sharing of Your Personal Information
BBO may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on BBO or the Site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of BBO and our family of Web sites; or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of BBO products or members of the public.
BBO may also disclose your personal information to cooperate with our partners in abuse-related investigations. For instance: ACBL requires that BBO report the names of players who have been banned from ACBL games.
Control of Your Personal Information
Except as otherwise described in this statement, personal information you provide on the Site will not be shared outside of BBO and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your permission.
Please be aware that this privacy statement and any choices you make on the Site will not necessarily apply to personal information you may have provided to BBO in the context of other, separately operated, BBO products or services.
Security of Your Personal Information
BBO is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. Additionally, when we transmit sensitive personal information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
The public portion of your profile (Name, email, country, skill level, other information) will be visible to every other member of the site.
Our support staff and some of our yellow volunteers can look up your IP address and, in addition, identity other aliases that you have might have used previously.
Our support staff can look up your entire profile, aliases, purchase history and chatlogs. Our accounting staff can look up your prior transactions (including yourreal name, address and phone number, if you supplied this information during commerce).
Destruction of Your Personal Information
BBO routinely discards system logs and other records after approximately 100 days.
Parts of some logs ( for example: those relating to commerce, technical support, and some account activity ) are kept indefinitely. Usernames can be disabled but not destroyed.
Use of Local Storage
We sometimes use your local storage ( typically, your hard drive ) to store your preferences (for example: screen size, screen position ).
If you choose to have the Site remember your username and password, the Site will encrypt these fields weakly and save them in local storage.
Your chat logs, including your private chat logs, are recorded
to local storage in some versions of the Site.
You have the ability to direct that these versions of the Site stop recording chat. You also have the abilty to erase previously logged chat. Both can be found in the Preferences section of the Site.
Some versions of the Site grant you the ability to automatically save hands that you have either played or viewed.
You have the ability to specify that these versions of the Site stop recording hands. This can be specified in the Preferences section of the Site.
Links to Other Web Sites
This site may contain links to other Web sites. Please be aware that this privacy statement applies solely to the information collected by the Site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other Web sites.
Use of Cookies
We sometimes use cookies on this Site to ensure the integrity of the login/registration process and to personalize the Site.
A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of delivering relevant content, eases site navigation, and so on. When you return to the web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the site's features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to use interactive features of this or other web sites that depend on cookies.
Changes to this Privacy Statement
We may occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the last updated date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this privacy statement, we will notify you either by placing a prominent notice on our site or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.
Contact Information
BBO welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you have questions about this statement or believe that we have not adhered to it, please contact us by clicking here.
You may also contact us through postal mail at the address provided below and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Bridge Base Online Ltd
2805 High Sail Court
Las Vegas, NV
USA 89117
© 2018-2020 Bridge Base On Line LLC •
About •
Privacy •
Rules •
